When I was little,
I visited mountains in the countryside
with my relatives for the first time.
Oh man, camping is so cool!
Raion, wanna see some fireworks?
Yeah, for sure!
Century Fireworks
Huh?
Did I forget to light it?
Raion, are you sure you lit them?
G-Gotcha! I never lit the fireworks!
What?!
Look at you, covering your ears like that!
Stop joking around!
Fine, I'll go light them.
Wait right there.
Huh?
Kazuki!
Raion!
Hey, Raion! You listening?
Hey! This is payback for Atsushi!
Get real! This all happened because of you!
The local hoodlums have been
fighting a lot recently...
You've been spreading lies to
put them up to it, haven't you?
You shouldn't get involved with me anymore.
You know, I can tell you still
feel guilty about the accident.
The one with the fireworks, I mean.
Let it go already.
Kazuki, that's not it—
I was being too careless.
The adults should've been
keeping an eye on us, too.
That's that. I've told you this before.
Kazuki, I...
For what it's worth,
I like the lies you tell.
What?
Not that your recent lies
have been totally innocent,
but the way I see it, you usually lie
from a place of goodwill and kindness.
Virtue won't get you
through everything in life.
Sometimes, you need to
set a thief to catch a thief!
I like the idea of a hero
using dirty tactics.
What are you talking about?
What I mean is, Raion...
Don't ever change yourself.
I was able to be myself through it all
thanks to Kazuki's words...
Tasuketsu
We will now begin tallying the majority.
Emperor!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
I see.
Isn't that enough of a reason
to join you guys?
I'm no athlete by any means, but
I'm confident that I've got decent brains.
Sure, as you just demonstrated.
Thanks for letting me join the group.
Very well, Raion Ouno!
I, Emperor Rahazelt,
shall welcome you into our gro—
Can we just cut the act already?
Wha?!
I'm going to go check on Kunashiri.
Even though Souma and
Nihonyanagi are with her,
she took what happened pretty hard.
Well sure...
That definitely wasn't a pretty sight...
By the way,
do you have anyone else in your group
besides the five of you?
Oh, right...
We have three others
who are in the Tohoku region.
And four others who are technically
supposed to be missing...
Supposed to be?
I'll tell you since it's just
the two of us here.
Our leader, Saneatsu, and his lieutenant,
Saaya, are actually both dead.
This is a secret between Team Saneatsu,
who directly fought the Emperor.
The only ones who know besides me are Ryuta,
Omi, and Rika, who went to Tohoku together.
I get it.
You needed to prevent a decline in morale.
You catch on quick, for real.
What about the other two?
Judging from Eren's account,
Kazuhiko's probably dead, too...
There's one person that's actually missing.
What's their name?
Tojuro Yagihashi.
We're not even sure what
he was last doing...
Then he could very well still be alive.
Nishime here.
All clear here on the second
floor's front desk. Over.
Raion here. Roger that.
All clear over here, for real!
Looks like Gobo's good, too.
The declaration of battle from the Queen...
We'll ignore it this time and force them
to go on air one more time.
Force them? But how?
We'll air the Emperor's
message as usual tonight.
I see. That way, the Queen will assume that
we didn't tune in to her message
from this afternoon.
Right, and they'll head back
to KHN a second time,
during the same window as
the Emperor's usual announcement.
So we'll be there to
ambush them when they do?
Are you sure it'll be that easy?
I wouldn't be surprised if they have
full knowledge of our tactics...
There's no doubt they've got
the guns to back it up.
Good evening, this is your Emperor.
Time to announce today's results.
As the current Emperor, Gobo will stay here.
Eren and Shinozaki, you two stay
as his bodyguards.
Nishime will take the front desk,
and Souma and I will be in the
Monitor Room to look over the station.
Gobo, keep an eye on the security
cameras outside the building.
We'll need to watch for their combat strength.
But with me on-site, we can edge
them out with quicker decision-making.
23:30 PM...
Look out.
I see human shadows on outside cameras.
They're here!
Raion, I hear footsteps!
Impossible! They're
at the front desk already?!
Nishime! Get out of there! Hurry!
What was that? What happened?!
You sure that wasn't a little overboard?
All this rubble is annoying.
We've been dispatched for a mission.
Why not make a scene?
So... where do you think the current
Emperor's subordinates are?
The Monitor Room, obviously.
Shoot! They blocked the exit...
Is there another way out?
But... they're right there!
I don't have any time to waste!
Right of Priority: Prioritize the
sound of rubble within this room.
Idiot! What are you doing?!
Get out of there!
Raion, Souma.
Get out safe.
Prioritize physical safety!
Found ya!
Or so you think!
What's up with him?
Jeez, he's all hurt...
not that I'm surprised.
He's probably just stupid.
This is fine...
I can buy time as long as
their focus is on me...
Run while you can... Souma! Raion!
If I can make my life mean something
for even one second...
Dying doesn't scare me one little bit!
Not exactly the thrill I was hoping for,
but I guess we gotta kill him...
Gotta play it safe, in case there's others.
Too bad for you, I work alone—
Kinda harsh to say right in front of us.
You guys! Why?!
Hey, Nishime.
Next time you try to off yourself
like that, I'll beat you up!
You look like you're ready to fight.
Now that's more like it.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Prime Right of Materialization!
Auto Shield!
Production Attribute!
This is trouble...
Can you walk, Nishime?!
Let's get outta here!
Souma can only materialize one more time...
He doesn't have the stamina to fight!
Not so fast!
It's a homing shield!
Hurry!
What are chairs doing out here?
The fire hydrant!
Could that be...
That guy's Prime Right is...
That was easy.
This is as far as you got?
Like I thought... he controls water!
This is bad...
The water supply is still
functioning normally...
Which makes... the entire city his weapon!
You've got one shield.
So we just have to outnumber you.
Teleportation?!
You're dealing with two officers
working under the Queen.
Give it up!
Wanna bet how many strikes it'll take?!
Prime Right of Materialization!
Black Knight!
I'll take care of him!
You two get out of here!
What are you talking about?!
You're at your limit!
What else can you do?!
Hey now...
Take my stamina out of the equation
and he's no match for me.
Souma... don't tell me...
No... that's my part.
Raion! Don't say tha—
Excuse me, guys!
Huh? Wait, what?
A Prime Right that switches places?!
So that's how she got here
from the station in a split second...!
Attack! Bla—
No! Stop!
Her power is to switch
places between objects!
She'll use her powers if you attack
and you'll hit one of us!
Fine then... As long as I leave her alone,
that's one less thing to worry about.
Ugh, figured you'd say that.
I hate being underestimated.
Right of Duplication!
Go on and kill him.
Black Knight! Defend!
There, now no one's standing in the way.
Ikusa! Let's take down this entire block!
Nice. Roger that.
This entire block?!
We've been sandwiched!
If this chick duplicates this guy's blow,
we'll get attacked from both sides!
Prime Right of Water Utilization!
Here's a little bonus!
Right of Adjustment!
Freeze!
Right of Duplication!
Shoot!
Prime Right of—
We'll be your shield.
I'm leaving the group to you, Souma.
Right of Priority...
Prioritize Souma's safety.
Not a bad way to go out, right Kazuki?
Mission complete.
Let's go home and report to Lady Kisaragi.
You scared me for a second there.
Looks like you think you
finished the job, but...
Wha—
I reject!
Ryuta! Omi! Rika!
You guys are back!
Who the hell are you?
Are you serious?!
He's Shuji Nihonyanagi-san!
One of the volunteers
from our ambush operation!
Oh yeah, that's right!
These guys... so they're
the ones who were in Tohoku.
I've got a lot of questions, but...
We'll deal with them first.
Hang on!
The guy can control water with
his Prime Right of Water Utilization
and he possesses the Adjustment Right.
The chick can switch places
with her Prime Right
and her Duplication Right can copy objects!
Cool, thanks!
All right gang, you know what to do!
Sure thing.
Mm-yup!
Backup, huh?
Then I'll kill you all together!
Prime Right of Evasion!
Wha—?!
Ikusa, your control is all over the place.
Fine, I guess I'll—
Hey, Miss!
Ya planning to come near me
or switch places with me?
What a drag. Of course!
Why did I say that?!
I reject!
Brat! What do you mean you "reject"?!
Prime Right of Exchange...
It's not working?!
So that's what Lady Kisaragi
was talking about!
The quasi-major Prime Right of Rejection!
That should make our defenses perfect.
All right, Ryuta. Wanna finish things off?
Sure.
Spring formation.
Ryuta Ichinose, ready for liftoff!
Prime Right of Fusion!
I'll separate them from Souma
and the guys with these pillars!
Ready for the finale?!
Hey! Not bad, dude!
Question time!
Would you rather keep playing? Or get lost?
Your choice.
If I was just a millisecond late...
Meguru! Let's retreat!
Agreed.
Th-Thank God!
They got rid of them like it was nothing...
So this is... what it means
to be a main-force unit!
Welcome home!
Mm-yup!
You see, Raion...
You noticed we were in trouble
on your device
and took a chance to send help
with your Presentation Right. I know.
He spoils everything, for real...
We were lucky you three were nearby.
So, I've heard lots about you.
Raion Ouno, was it?
I hear you're our newest member.
That's right! For real!
I'm confident he can fill Narita's shoes.
Sane's?
No way this little kid could
take Sane's place, ever.
Ryuta...
He was my best friend,
and our one and only leader.
Are you good with sports and studies?
Huh?
Just answer the question.
Well, no... I guess I'm not
the athletic type...
So you're only half as good!
Sane was good at both sports and studies!
Only good at studying?!
So you've got no chops for battle!
Sorry bud, you lose!
Get real, you idiot!
Sane? I don't even know who that is!
I'm me and no one else!
Are we being a bit jealous?
Don't be lame, now.
Shaddup!
That's a relief.
Huh?
I'd rather be friends with
someone with a few flaws
rather than the cool and collected type.
After all, we're all here
to complement each other.
Immaturity can be a unique trait, I guess.
Well, I'm in 8th grade,
so I'm technically not mature.
Huh?
You're in 8th grade?!
I'm in 8th grade too!
I wasn't asking you, idiot!
Oh yeah?!
What is that?!
The Emperor's tower...
That's where we fought the Emperor.
Fought the Emperor...
Sane, Saaya, and the Emperor's bodies
are still at the top of the tower.
The lower levels are covered in rubble,
so we can't get to them.
We were talking about trying
to climb to the top when we get back.
It's been a whole month, and
with this hot summer weather...
They've probably already decomposed.
We may be better off not looking.
But... I've gotta see them.
I have to face reality
and accept it to move on.
I'm still not able to accept
that Sane died...
But that's not right. He sacrificed
his life to defeat the Emperor.
Now it's my turn to do the same
and defeat the Queen.
For that, I need to see it
with my own eyes,
and accept that Sane's gone,
so I can take on this next opponent!
Have courage!
Face the truth!
Goodbye... Sane...
W-What's wrong, Ryuta-kun?
They haven't decomposed...
Sane and Saaya, they're still
the same as that day...
Impossible!
You're right... it's like they're asleep.
But that's... how's that possible?
I knew it!
The Emperor's body is... gone!
Then that means...
The Emperor's...
Shock
...still alive?!